{
    "subject": "T._B._Walker",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Harriet_G._Walker",
    "human_readable": "T.B. Walker is married to Harriet G. Walker.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9858351349830627,
            "question": "Is there a marriage relationship between T.B. Walker and Harriet G. Walker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9685127139091492,
            "question": "Who is married to Harriet G. Walker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9461020231246948,
            "question": "To whom is T.B. Walker married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.935445249080658,
            "question": "Is T.B. Walker married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8743199110031128,
            "question": "What is the relationship between T.B. Walker and Harriet G. Walker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8607959747314453,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Harriet G. Walker's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8583737015724182,
            "question": "What is the name of Harriet G. Walker's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7547928690910339,
            "question": "Who is T.B. Walker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7252643704414368,
            "question": "What is the marital status of T.B. Walker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06834162026643753,
            "question": "Who are the individuals mentioned in this statement?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=T.B. Walker is married to Harriet G. Walker.",
            "html": "yago_14553_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the marital status of T.B. Walker?",
            "html": "yago_14553_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is T.B. Walker?",
            "html": "yago_14553_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Harriet G. Walker's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_14553_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14553_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14553_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14553_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14553_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14553_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14553_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14553_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14553_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14553_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14553_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain multiple references to a Thomas B. Walker (T.B. Walker) who was married to Harriet, with various details about their life and family, including the fact that they had eight children together."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"T.B. Walker is married to Harriet G. Walker.\" Specifically, document `29.txt` states \"Walker married Harriet Granger Hulet (1841-1917) on December 19, 1863,\" and documents `57.txt`, `82.txt`, and `83.txt` all mention her as his wife."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}